[ED]
Ah, it's filming.
Oh, I got it.
Ta-da!
Today
We are filming.
National Never Lose Tour
I did the shoot and got my makeup done like this just now.
I was the early one in line, so I was still the first one to adjust, so it was a wait.
I wasn't sure if I wanted to wear my bangs down.
Today turned out to be a happy day!
Ta-da!
I'm listening to a song right now.
I can see your shoulders like this.
I don't know what to call it.
I don't know...
It's kind of cool.
The plan is to have half of my face darkened.
Now I'm planning to do it with the baby...
Yuna-nyanesu!
of the tour
visual
It's a photo shoot!
Yay!
I'm feeling pretty plain today.
My makeup is
Straight.
That's right, everyone is straight.
You were straight in that one, too, right?
What was it?
When we shot here
When we did Goldischer.
Yeah.
Your major label debut?
It was your major label debut.
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Mr. Tork is straight these days.
Like half of straight, he's super flashy when he performs live.
Everyone else is straight, but we're not so much.
We don't have that much. We tend to curl our hair a lot.
We arrange it. We're gals.
We've had a lot of gigs recently, so it's been fun to get a lot of different hairstyles.
The back is kind of nice.
It's pink and pretty.
Good morning.
Good morning. - Good morning.
G'morning.
Gmoronie. Hi, Gmoronie.
I'm the guy who's leaving now and the guy who's filming.
Heh.
That's great.
Hello.
Thank you.
I think he's watching.
Rice balls?
I don't know if it's your first time.
I think you do.
I'm hungry.
I'm going out to eat.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
This is my first time in Hiroshima.
You're going on tour.
You're going back, right?
I didn't get to see the sights.
I want to go there.
It's beautiful.
I'd love to.
What else?
I don't know.
I've never been to Chiba.
Yes, and the lyrics, too.
Chiba started it casually
Chiba looked like a young man in front of the shine
Look, the no-makeup real version
In fact, it takes a long time to do this!
Funny!
Unevenness is so cute!
Now, you know, I just did a little funder.
I'm done with the makeup, I'm all set.
Yay!
I was a bit of a hitter, today.
Eh, it was different, wasn't it?
It was something, I was there when I came in.
I already had my makeup on.
I even put on eyeliner.
I hadn't actually done that recently.
When you put in an inet, you get to be on camera a lot.
I'm going to get a lot of camera time.
It's you.
That's it. That's it.
Alone. Not at all.
Onigiriman.
I'll be at the Onigiriman Center.
Bye, Onigiriman.
Bye bye.
ammunition ammunition
the may
Today's guest for Hitori Nabe, Katamimi Nabe is Hina Suzuki.
And joining us with the voice of heaven, NAGARA SAKURA Hina-san.
This is Ten-san.
Today's nabe is called Se-no, Hinachan nabe!
There is a commonality among them.
I would like to talk a lot while eating the smell of feeling nabe, se-o, chicken bread.
Then, I would like to draw a subject. Se-no, what happened recently!
What happened recently?
Well, you know...
Things are going pretty well.
Things are going well.
I'd like to introduce our guest, Mizuki Hika.
Hello.
What is it?
Even if you don't wear any makeup...
It's nice.
When you give it to me...
Teeth.
That's good.
Too small.
He's a celebrity.
Oh, uh, he's a newborn.
Good morning.
I'm back from the shoot.
When I came back from the shoot...
Shinjuku.
I was doing Roboko.
I'm doing two things now.
Yes, you were doing it.
Thank you, you made it easier to think when I didn't see Miu Miu.
We're chatting now, talking about my past.
I reminded him that I've never been in a squadron in my life and I wanted to be in a squadron.
Then you guys did a metaphor.
He said he wanted to be the chairman of the committee, so he ran for it, but he ended up being the vice chairman.
They didn't want me to mention that and told me to go for it.
I wanted him to mention it.
I asked him about it, and he said it was private and I shouldn't mention it.
It was a good visit.
Thank you very much.
I think by the time they're moving up, they'll have decided who's going to be a player.